{
  "translations": {
    "en": {
      "q4": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Lets take some examples to make things more easy. Suppose that $L_1 = \\{fish, dog, carrot\\}$ and that $L_2 = \\{rot\\}$.",
        "question": "What are the words in $L_1$ that end with words in $L_2$?",
        "answer": "carrot",
        "choices": ["fish", "dog", "carrot"]
      },
      "q5": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "The definition for $L_1 \\backslash L_2 = \\{x\\ |\\ xy \\in L_1$ for some $\\ y \\in L_2\\}$",
        "question": "What are the words in $L_1 \\backslash L_2$?",
        "answer": "car",
        "choices": ["fish", "dog", "carrot", "car"]
      },
      "q7": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Lets take another example. Suppose that $L_1 = \\{carrot, parrot, rot\\}$ and that $L_2 = \\{rot\\}$.",
        "question": "What are the words in $L_1$ that end with words in $L_2$?",
        "answer": ["carrot", "parrot", "rot"],
        "choices": ["carrot", "parrot", "rot"]
      },
      "q8": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "The definition for $L_1 \\backslash L_2 = \\{x\\ |\\ xy \\in L_1$ for some $\\ y \\in L_2\\}$",
        "question": "What are the words in $L_1 \\backslash L_2$?",
        "answer": ["$\\lambda$", "car", "par"],
        "choices": ["carrot", "parrot", "rot", "$\\lambda$", "car", "par"]
      },
      "q9": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Suppose that $L_1 = \\{carrot\\}$ and that $L_2 = \\{t, ot\\}$.",
        "question": "What are the words in $L_1 \\backslash L_2$?",
        "answer": ["carr", "carro"],
        "choices": ["carrot", "car", "rot", "$\\lambda$", "carr", "carro"]
      },
      "q10": {
        "type": "select",
        "description": "Suppose that $L_1 = \\{cab, dab\\}$ and that $L_2 = \\{b, ab\\}$.",
        "question": "What are the words in $L_1 \\backslash L_2$?",
        "answer": ["c", "d", "ca", "da"],
        "choices": ["a", "b", "c", "d", "ca", "da", "cab", "dab"]
      },
      "q11": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "The definition for $L_1 \\backslash L_2 = \\{x\\ |\\ xy \\in L_1$ for some $\\ y \\in L_2\\}$",
        "question": "Select the correct answer. If $\\lambda \\in L_2$, which of the following is a part of the $L_1 \\backslash L_2$?",
        "answer": "$L_1$",
        "choices": ["$L_2$", "$L_1$", "$\\lambda$" ]
      },
      "q12": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Suppose that $L_1 = \\{a^*b^* \\cup b^*a^*\\}$ and that $L_2 = \\{b^n\\ |\\ n$ is even, $n > 0 \\}$.",
        "question": "What are the words in $L_1 \\backslash L_2$?",
        "answer": "$\\{a^*b^*\\}$",
        "choices": ["$\\{a^*b^*\\}$","$\\{b^*a^*\\}$", "$\\{b^n\\ |\\ n$ is even, $n > 0 \\}$"]
      },
      "q14": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "To prove that we need to construct a DFA $M\\prime=(Q, \\Sigma, \\delta, q_0, F\\prime)$ where $M = (Q, \\Sigma, \\delta, q_0, F)$ is the DFA for $L_1$.",
        "question": "What is the difference between $M$ (the DFA for $L_1$) and $M\\prime$ (the DFA for $L_1 \\backslash L_2$)?",
        "answer": "different final states",
        "choices": ["They are identical", "differnt transition function", "different states", "different final states"]
      },
      "q17": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Let us test every state to see if it has a walk labled with strings $\\in L_2 = \\{b^m\\ |\\ m \\ge 1 \\}$ to any final state",
        "question": "Is there a walk to a final state labeled with one or more $b$'s for $q_0$?",
        "answer": "No",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q18": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Remember that:<br/>The algorithm is: for each state $q_i$, if there is a walk labeled with strings $\\in L_2$ to a final state in $M$, we mark $q_i$ as final state.",
        "question": "Should $q_0$ be a final state?",
        "answer": "No",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q19": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Let us test every state to see if it has a walk labled with strings $\\in L_2 = \\{b^m\\ |\\ m \\ge 1 \\}$ to any final state",
        "question": "Is there a walk to a final state labeled with one or more $b$'s for $q_1$?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q20": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Remember that:<br/>The algorithm is: for each state $q_i$, if there is a walk labeled with strings $\\in L_2$ to a final state in $M$, we mark $q_i$ as final state.",
        "question": "Should $q_1$ be a final state?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q21": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Let us test every state to see if it has a walk labled with strings $\\in L_2 = \\{b^m\\ |\\ m \\ge 1 \\}$ to any final state",
        "question": "Is there a walk to a final state labeled with one or more $b$'s for $q_2$?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q22": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Remember that:<br/>The algorithm is: for each state $q_i$, if there is a walk labeled with strings $\\in L_2$ to a final state in $M$, we mark $q_i$ as final state.",
        "question": "Should $q_2$ be a final state?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q23": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Let us test every state to see if it has a walk labled with strings $\\in L_2 = \\{b^m\\ |\\ m \\ge 1 \\}$ to any final state",
        "question": "Is there a walk to a final state labeled with one or more $b$'s for $q_3$?",
        "answer": "No",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q24": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Remember that:<br/>The algorithm is: for each state $q_i$, if there is a walk labeled with strings $\\in L_2$ to a final state in $M$, we mark $q_i$ as final state.",
        "question": "Should $q_3$ be a final state?",
        "answer": "No",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q25": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Let us test every state to see if it has a walk labled with strings $\\in L_2 = \\{b^m\\ |\\ m \\ge 1 \\}$ to any final state",
        "question": "Is there a walk to a final state labeled with one or more $b$'s for $q_4$?",
        "answer": "No",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q26": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Remember that:<br/>The algorithm is: for each state $q_i$, if there is a walk labeled with strings $\\in L_2$ to a final state in $M$, we mark $q_i$ as final state.",
        "question": "Should $q_4$ be a final state?",
        "answer": "No",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q27": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Let us test every state to see if it has a walk labled with strings $\\in L_2 = \\{b^m\\ |\\ m \\ge 1 \\}$ to any final state",
        "question": "Is there a walk to a final state labeled with one or more $b$'s for $q_5$?",
        "answer": "No",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q28": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Remember that:<br/>The algorithm is: for each state $q_i$, if there is a walk labeled with strings $\\in L_2$ to a final state in $M$, we mark $q_i$ as final state.",
        "question": "Should $q_5$ be a final state?",
        "answer": "No",
        "choices": ["Yes", "No"]
      },
      "q31": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "Let us do the last example. Suppose that $L_1 = \\{a^*baa^*\\}$ and $L_2 = \\{ab^*\\}$. We need to find $L_1 \\backslash L_2$",
        "question": "Which DFA we should build first?",
        "answer": "DFA for $L_1$",
        "choices": ["DFA for $L_1$", "DFA for $L_2$", "DFA for $L_1 \\backslash L_2$"]
      },      
      "q33": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "The formal proof is:<br/>For each state $i$ do<br/>$\\ \\ \\ \\ $Make $i$ the start state that represent $L_i\\prime$<br/>$\\ \\ \\ \\ $if $L_i\\prime \\cap L_2 \\ne \\emptyset$ then<br/>$\\ \\ \\ \\ \\ \\ \\ \\ $put $i$ in $F\\prime$ in $M\\prime$<br/>where $M\\prime$ is the DFA for $L_1 \\backslash L_2$",
        "question": "Let $L_0\\prime$ to be the Language that represented by the DFA where $q_0$ is the start state. Should $q_0$ be a final state?",
        "answer": "No",
        "choices": ["No", "Yes"]
      },
      "q34": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "The formal proof is:<br/>For each state $i$ do<br/>$\\ \\ \\ \\ $Make $i$ the start state that represent $L_i\\prime$<br/>$\\ \\ \\ \\ $if $L_i\\prime \\cap L_2 \\ne \\emptyset$ then<br/>$\\ \\ \\ \\ \\ \\ \\ \\ $put $i$ in $F\\prime$ in $M\\prime$<br/>where $M\\prime$ is the DFA for $L_1 \\backslash L_2$",
        "question": "Let $L_1\\prime$ to be the Language that represented by the DFA where $q_1$ is the start state. Should $q_1$ be a final state?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "choices": ["No", "Yes"]
      },
      "q35": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "The formal proof is:<br/>For each state $i$ do<br/>$\\ \\ \\ \\ $Make $i$ the start state that represent $L_i\\prime$<br/>$\\ \\ \\ \\ $if $L_i\\prime \\cap L_2 \\ne \\emptyset$ then<br/>$\\ \\ \\ \\ \\ \\ \\ \\ $put $i$ in $F\\prime$ in $M\\prime$<br/>where $M\\prime$ is the DFA for $L_1 \\backslash L_2$",
        "question": "Let $L_2\\prime$ to be the Language that represented by the DFA where $q_2$ is the start state. Should $q_2$ be a final state?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "choices": ["No", "Yes"]
      },
      "q36": {
        "type": "multiple",
        "description": "The formal proof is:<br/>For each state $i$ do<br/>$\\ \\ \\ \\ $Make $i$ the start state that represent $L_i\\prime$<br/>$\\ \\ \\ \\ $if $L_i\\prime \\cap L_2 \\ne \\emptyset$ then<br/>$\\ \\ \\ \\ \\ \\ \\ \\ $put $i$ in $F\\prime$ in $M\\prime$<br/>where $M\\prime$ is the DFA for $L_1 \\backslash L_2$",
        "question": "Let $L_3\\prime$ to be the Language that represented by the DFA where $q_3$ is the start state. Should $q_3$ be a final state?",
        "answer": "No",
        "choices": ["No", "Yes"]
      }
    }
  }
}
